你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
-西沃恩  -你他妈离我远点
- Siobhan. - Stay the fuck away from me.
你耍了我们  我  布罗克  艾米特
You played us. Me, Brock, Emmett.
你的一切都是假的
Everything about you is a lie.
西沃恩  听我说
Siobhan, listen to me.
不要动
Don't.
好  好
Okay. Okay.
好
Okay.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
是我  西沃恩
It's me, Siobhan.
听到了吗
You hear me?
是我啊
It's me.
别这样
Come on.
只是我
It's just me.
你根本不存在
There is no you.
让我一个人静静  你出去
I need time to think. Just get out.
我们该谈谈
We should talk about this.
给我滚出去
Get the fuck out!
快滚
Now!
-晚上好  -马里奥和弗兰克呢
- Hey, good evening. - Where's Mario and Frank?
他们在雷默广场那边加班呢
Oh, um, they had to do a double at Raymor Plaza.
好像是水管泄漏了
Some kind of plumbing leak.
他们正搞得浑身是屎呢  真的
They're up to their eyeballs in shit, literally.
-是啊  -把你们的证件给我
- Yeah. - Give me your badges.
我们都已经扫描过了
We already scanned them.
我要再扫描一次
And I'm gonna scan them again.
请原谅我的朋友
Excuse my friend.
事故之后他反应就有点迟钝了
He's a little slow since the accident.
怎么  出问题了吗
What? Something wrong?
你为什么把头发剪了  伙计
Why'd you cut your hair, man?
什么
What?
原来是爆炸头
The 'fro.
我总跟秃子在一块儿
You know, just hanging around guys like this,
留个爆炸头好像在炫耀似的
it just felt too much like showing off.
谢谢
Thanks.
晚上愉快
Have a good night.
谢谢  你也是
Yeah, thank you. You, too.
好了
Okay.
大哥们在安保室
Big Brother's in the house.
你看到我看到的画面了吗
You seeing what I'm seeing?
操  他们目不转睛地盯着显示器
Shit, they're watching them monitors like hawks.
那咱们就换换画面
Then let's change the view.
好啊
All right.
你那边安全了  去弄那个公式吧
Okay, you're clear. Go get that formula.
-那是个算法  -咱说的是一回事
- It's an algorithm. - Yeah, you say tomato.
有个警卫正往那边走
Hey, one of the guards is on the move.
-你最好抓紧时间  -你别瞎叨叨了
- You better step on it. - You need to step off it.
我又不是在这里看视频  可以快进
I ain't watching fucking YouTube videos up in here.
他上电梯了
Damn, he's getting on the elevator.
-你搭档呢  -去方便了
- Where's your partner? - Oh, he went to take a leak.
你懂的
You know?
你得加把劲了  伙计
Look, you better step on it, man.
马上就有人过去了
Gonna get real crowded in there real soon.
欧了
Got you.
贾伯
Job.
-抱歉我迟到了  -45分钟了  卡莉
- Sorry I'm late. - 45 minutes, Carrie.
她的老师等不了这么久
Her teacher couldn't wait.
她怎么说
What did she say?
说蒂法不交作业  上课捣乱
Well, Deva's missing assignments, she's disruptive in class,
态度也很差
and basically her attitude sucks.
学校明显觉得我们的女儿
And apparently the school feels that our daughter
在家里没人管教
is lacking any kind of discipline or structure at home.
-这是我的错吗  -我没指责你
- And that's my fault? - I'm not pointing fingers.
你就是在指责我  你自己可是个嫖妓的市长
Well, you just did and this from a mayor who bangs hookers.
那抛弃家庭  跑去追杀自己的黑道父亲
Yeah, and like abandoning your family to go off to hunt down
就是我们宣扬的家庭价值观了吗
your gangster father is a lesson in family values?
你去死吧  戈登
Fuck you, Gordon.
卡莉  求你别这样了好吗
Carrie, can you stop, please?
我们需要做得更好
Look, we need to do better.
我知道我在为自己处理不好所发生的事
I realize that I have been blaming everybody else
而责怪身边的所有人
for my inability to handle everything that's happened.
我只是...这是我们的家
I just-- it's our family.
你知道我此前从未当过受害者
But you know that I have never been a victim in my life
我已经受够了
and I'm done with that.
我想为了我们所有人  解决这件事
I want to figure this out for all of us.
在我家乡有这么个习俗
Where I come from, it's customary
圆满完成工作后得喝一杯
to drink to a job well done.
完成
Done?
那个算法只是这个混账群集的小提示
That algorithm was just the tip of this cluster fuck.
不  这是个小胜利  可以激励我们继续前进
No, it's the small victories that keep you in the fight.
我知道你号称是梅伯里地区的活佛什么的
I know you the Dalai Lama of Mayberry and all that shit,
但这不代表你说的话都是真理
but that don't mean everything coming out your mouth is wisdom.
现在离庆祝还远着呢
It is far from party time.
好吧
Fine.
干杯
Cheers.
你这次又惹着谁了
Who'd you piss off this time?
我们可能得跑了
We may have to bail.
你是说不要这活了
What, on the job?
什么都不要了
On everything.
真的什么都不要了
Everything everything?
有多严重
How bad is it?
-西沃恩手里有我的案底  -我靠
- Siobhan has the police file on me. - Oh, fuck.
那我们现在怎么还不赶快离开这鬼地方
So why aren't we already doing 95 out of this shithole?
可能因为她不会告发我
Could be she won't turn me in.
我给你说说明白
Let me explain something to you.
假条子  也就是你
There are fake cops-- that's you--
真条子  也就是她
and there are real cops-- that's her.
区别就是真条子会把你丫交出去
Difference being real cops will turn your ass in.
也可能不会
Maybe not.
你能不能告诉这个人
Would you please tell this man
想收手不干早他妈晚了
it is way past time to cut and fuckin' run?
你们俩做好要做的事
You two both do what you gotta do.
但我该去工作了  贾伯
But I'm going to work, Job.
宝贝  我希望你用力的回想
Baby, I want you to try real hard
上一次你在女人身上孤注一掷
to remember what happened
后果怎么样
the last time you rolled the dice on a woman.
去他妈的  我走了
Fuck this. I'm packing.
-你准备什么时候告诉我  -布罗克
- When were you gonna tell me? - Brock.
你现在都开始为普罗科特工作了
You're working for Proctor now,
艾米丽  你疯了吗
Emily? Have you lost it?
你怎么会知道的
How could you possibly know that?
-我给你的中介打电话了  -你干嘛了
- I called your agency. - You did what?
-我没有你的消息  -老天啊  布罗克
- I didn't hear from you. - Jesus Christ, Brock.
-我是在担心你  -你是在监视我
- I was worried about you. - You're spying on me.
-我不是监视你  -你太不可以理喻了
- I'm not spying on you. - You're unbelievable.
你知道普罗科特有多危险吗
Do you have any idea how dangerous Proctor is?
知道他和哪些人来往吗
The kind of people that he deals with?
结果你现在还跑到他家去了
And now you're living in the goddamn house?
他母亲要死了
His mother is dying.
没错  但要死的也不是她一个
Yeah, well, apparently she's not the only one.
之前我在他家
I was there the other day
从泳池里捞出一具帮派分子的尸体
fishing a dead gangbanger out of his pool.
小艾  那里很危险
Em, bad things happen there.
我关心病人
I care for the dying.
那是我的工作
That's what I do.
我以后也会如此
That's what I'm gonna keep on doing.
听着  小艾  我求你了
Listen. Em, I'm begging you.
离那个人越远越好
Get as far away from that man as possible.
我唯一该远离的人  是你
The only one I need to get away from is you.
艾米丽
Emily.
很有意思
That's very interesting.
事态有变就给我打电话
Just call me if anything changes.
汤米·里特斯通的遗体已经准许释放
Tommy Littlestone's body has been cleared for release.
我肯定他的兄弟
I'm pretty sure his brother's
迫切地希望马上把他带回居留地
eager to get him back to the reservation.
我也想去
I want to go, too.
可以
All right.
谢谢  叔叔
Thank you, Uncle.
我妈快把我逼疯了
My mother is driving me crazy.
我做什么她都不顺眼
She's got a problem with everything I do.
什么时候想跟我换妈  说一声就行
Any time you want to trade moms, just say the word.
抱歉
Sorry.
我不觉得
Yeah, didn't think so.
麦克斯怎么样
How is Max doing?
大概还不错吧
Fine, I guess.
麦克斯想要这个游戏好几个月了
Max has been wanting that game for months.
-75美元买个游戏  什么鬼  -太疯狂了
- $75 for a video game? What the hell?  - It's crazy.
她怎么样了
How's she doing?
舒适地休息中
Resting comfortably.
新药止痛效果更好
The new meds are doing a better job with the pain.
很好
That's good.
谢谢你把她照顾得这么好
Thank you for taking such good care of her.
她应得的
Well, it's what she deserves.
我们都应得的
It's what we all deserve.
是啊
Yeah.
你怎么样  普罗科特先生
How are you holding up, Mr. Proctor?
我吗
Me?
快死的可不是我
Well, I'm not the one who's dying.
可你很痛苦  而这种疼痛无药可医
But you are suffering and you don't get any meds.
做为强者的坏处就是
The downside to being strong for everyone else
你永远没有自己的时间
is that you never get a moment for yourself.
如果你想聊聊天或者...
If you ever want to talk or...
反正我也没其它地方可去
I've got nowhere else to be.
过来坐坐吧
Do you want to sit down?
三号桌的苹果派
Apple on three.
六号桌已经可以点餐了
Table six is ready to order.
九号桌需要金属餐具
Table nine needs silverware.
十二桌的露营家需要第三次咖啡续杯
And the campers on 12 are asking for a third refill on coffee.
过来帮一下忙啊
A little help here.
十二桌还在等续杯
12 is still asking for that refill.
卡莉
Carrie.
-现在怎么办  -等
- What now? - We wait.
待在车里
Stay here.
上车
Get in.
我一直跟着我叔叔练习
I've been practicing with my uncle.
你没什么驾驶经验
You're not an experienced driver.
那就让我积累经验吧
Well, then let's go get me some experience.
搞什么
What the hell?
你找我  出什么事了
You called. What's going on?
我要撤回普罗科特的认罪协议
I'm withdrawing Proctor's plea bargain.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我们早上第一件事就是提出动议
We'll file the motion first thing in the morning.
斯柏林一定会发火的
Sperling is gonna go apeshit on us.
把这当做额外奖励吧
Well, that's just the gravy.
顺便说句抱歉  我之前是个蠢货
By the way, I'm sorry I was a jerk.
你不是蠢货
You weren't a jerk.
你是个混蛋
You were an asshole.
我该走了  你也好收拾下
I should probably go. Let you get settled.
看来你有秘密啊  头儿
You've got secrets, boss.
谁没有呢
Don't we all?
如果事情太多  或者你想找人谈谈
If they ever get to be too much or if you want to talk...
-明天见  -好吧
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Yeah.
我是西沃恩·凯利
Hi, you've reached Siobhan Kelly.
请留言
Please leave a message.
-胡德  -怎么了
- Hood. - Yeah?
我刚接到消防救援部的电话
I just got a call from Fire and Rescue.
六号公路上有事故
There's a wreck out on Highway 6.
你来处理
You handle it.
两人到医院时已死亡  都是红骨帮
Two DOAs, both Redbones.
他们在转移汤米·里特斯通的尸体
They were transporting Tommy Littlestone's body.
很好  走吧
Great, let's go.
龙舌兰酒  哪种的都行
Tequila. Whatever you got.
她要加冰的陈年龙舌兰
She'll have the Anejo, chilled.
好酒配佳人嘛
A real woman like you, I think that she deserves the best.
你请客吗
You buying?
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
来两杯吧
Make it a double.
一直上  别停
And keep 'em coming.
我还以为我今天最倒霉
I thought I was having a bad day.
什么情况
What do we got?
驾驶员是哈坎·埃文斯
Driver is Hakan Evans.
是他在停尸房签字领的尸体
He signed for the body at the morgue.
我们需要牙医记录来确认另一名死者
We'll need dental records to identify the other.
-有目击证人吗  -这地方可不会有
- Any witnesses? - Not out here.
第二组刹车痕迹表明当时还有其他车辆
A second set of skid marks confirms another vehicle was involved.
-很可能是场意外  -有可能
- Could have been an accident. - Yeah.
你知道这不是场意外
You know this wasn't an accident.
不是吗
No?
切顿会把这当成是对他的宣战
Chayton is gonna see this as a declaration of war.
就算是  也是普罗科特的事
Yeah, well, that's Proctor's problem.
我们怎么处理
Well, what are we gonna do about it?
-什么也不做  -什么
- Nothing. - What?
我们他妈的置身事外
We stay the fuck out of it.
这酒真爽
Ah, it burns so good.
你笑起来真的很美
You have a real pretty smile.
-我还是很有魅力  -没错  女士
- Yeah, I still got it. - Yes, ma'am.
那最好了
That's good.
你的摩托车停在外边了吗
Is that your bike parked outside?
性感的野兽  不是吗
Sexy beast, isn't she?
我以前也梦想过拥有那样一辆车
I used to dream about owning a machine like that.
为什么说是以前
What do you mean used to?
物是人非了
Another life.
那可是个悲惨的故事
Well, that is a terribly sad story.
不过不用担心  因为你的新朋友斯凯沃
But don't you worry 'cause your new buddy Scuyver,
他总是能带来愉快的结局
well, he's all about the happy endings.
是吗
Is that right?
没错
That is right.
我觉得
I think that...
也许我们该去更隐蔽一点的地方
maybe you and me should go somewhere more private.
听上去不错  不过还是算了
That sounds great, but, no.
我要走了
I gotta go.
-下次吧  -什么
- Maybe next time. - What?
为了这场欢聚我可是买了六杯酒
I got six drinks invested in this little party.
所以你哪也不能去
So you ain't going nowhere
除非你表示点感激之情
till you show me a little gratitude.
我说不  就是不
When I say no, I mean it.
我是西沃恩·凯利
Hi, you've reached Siobhan Kelly.
请留言
Please leave a message.
你在哪
Where are you?
你应该问我不在哪
You should be asking where I'm not.
因为20分钟之内
Because in 20 minutes,
我就会离开见鬼的宾州女妖镇了
the answer's gonna be Banshee, Pennsyl-fucking-vania.
等我到今天结束  我和你一起走
Give me until the end of the day and I'll come with you.
还有些琐碎的事要处理下
Just gotta tie up a few loose ends.
那你处理得快点  宝贝
Well, then you tie them up quick, baby,
我们好离开这鬼地方
and let's get the fuck out of here.
-蒂法  -干吗
- Hey, Deva. - What?
-你没去学校  -我只是晚了点
- You aren't in school. - I'm just running a little late.
也许是因为你走错方向了
Well, maybe that's 'cause you're going the wrong way.
-好像你没翘过课一样  -我没被抓过
- Like you never ditched. - I never got caught.
蒂法  那天的事对不起
Hey, Deva, I'm sorry about the other day.
已经过去了  好吗
I'm over it, seriously.
我不是有意气走你的
Look, I didn't mean to blow you off.
好吗  你来得太突然了
Okay? I-- you caught me off guard
我说错话了  真的对不起
and everything came out wrong and I'm sorry.
不会再有下次了
Well, it won't happen again, okay?
从今开始  你只是搞大我妈肚子的混蛋
From now on, you're just the asshole who knocked up my mom.
好吧  我是混蛋
Okay, fine, I'm the asshole.
自从我来  除了麻烦什么也没给你
I mean, I've caused you nothing but problems since I got here,
所以我理解
so I get it.
差不多吧
Pretty much.
我操
Fuck.
-你有什么好在乎的  -我就是在乎
- Why do you even care? - I just do.
为什么
Why?
我老爹从来没在乎过我
Look, my old man never gave a shit about me.
明白吗  我是说
All right? I mean...
你可以说他诚实
I guess you could call him honest.
但我最恨他这一点
But I fucking hated him for it.
现在还恨  我希望自己不恨了  但我恨
I still do. I wish I didn't, but I do.
我不希望你恨我  蒂法
I don't want you to hate me, Deva.
但我不能强迫你做任何事  谁都不行
But I can't make you do anything, no one can.
这种事要你自己做主
That's a choice you gotta make on your own.
你是不是要离开了
You're leaving, aren't you?
我必须离开
I have to.
如果我想让你留下  你会在乎吗
Does it matter that I want you to stay?
会
Yes.
我很在乎
It matters.
懂吗
Okay?
但是我捅了大篓子  孩子
But I made a huge fucking mess, kid.
我必须离开
And I have to go.
我不恨你
I don't hate you.
好吧  有一点点恨
Well, maybe a little bit.
我可以接受
I can live with that.
你他妈在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
杰克逊  你好  你有预约吗
Hi, Jackson. We have an appointment?
我们明明说好的
We had a goddamn deal.
好吧  我们立场变了
Yeah, well, our position has changed.
你不能这样做
You can't do this.
已经做了
It's already done.
普罗科特将会上法庭
Proctor will have his day in court.
戈登  你在犯大错
You're making a big mistake, Gordon.
杰克逊  小心说话  听起来几乎是威胁了
Careful, Jackson, that almost sounded like a threat.
这是警告
It's a warning.
我会不惜一切代价找你麻烦
I'm gonna come at you with everything I've got.
你要付出的代价是  输掉官司
Yeah, and what you've got is a guilty client.
你应该劝劝你老板
You should talk some sense into your boss.
这件事也会牵扯到你
Your ass is on the line here, too.
谢谢你的关心
I appreciate your concern.
油量表
该死
Shit.
你想谈谈吗
So you want to talk about it?
我太傻了  我只是有点得意忘形了
It was stupid. I just got carried away is all.
极限竞速5
我觉得被困住了
I feel trapped.
我不停地从梦中惊醒
I keep waking up from a dream
却意识到现实生活才是真正的噩梦
to realize that it's real life that's become the nightmare.
我就会做一些很危险很愚蠢的行为
Then I do these stupid, dangerous things.
我知道
I know that.
只是...我都快喘不过气来了
It's just... I need to breathe.
我知道那种感觉
Well, I know how that feels.
还好有你陪着我
It's good to have you around.
是啊
Yeah.
-说到这个  -什么
- About that. - What?
怎么了
What?
我知道这样很自私  但我不希望你离开
I know I'm being selfish, but I don't want you to go.
至少别这么快
Not now.
但其实已经别无选择了  对吗
Well, there's really no choice anymore, is there?
你真的觉得她会逮捕你吗
Do you really think she'd arrest you?
这已经不重要了
It doesn't really matter, does it?
她已经知道了
She knows.
你准备去哪里
Where are you gonna go?
我不知道
I don't know.
哪都可以
Anywhere.
好吧
Right.
蒂法
Deva.
她会没事的
She'll be okay.
她很坚强
She's strong.
像她妈妈
Like her mom.
那你呢
And what about you?
你会没事吗
Are you gonna be okay?
当然了
Of course.
你好像不是很开心  没事吧
You look upset. Everything okay?
会没事的
It'll be all right.
我们得谈谈学校的事
You know we have to talk about school.
是啊
Yeah.
但今晚算了
Not tonight, though.
好好休息吧
Get some sleep.
好的  晚安
Okay. Good night.
晚安
Good night.
你可以把衣服脱掉了
You can get undressed now.
你要走了
Are you leaving?
你想管红骨帮的事
You wanna take on the Redbones,
随你
go right ahead.
我不像你年轻气盛
I'm too old and too tired
我不想多管闲事
to be sticking my nose where it don't belong.
我们可是警察啊  卡尔
We're the goddamn police, Karl.
我要回家了
I'm going home.
除非这房子着火了  否则不要找我
Don't call me unless the building's on fire.
我还是觉得你没点警察的样子
I still don't think you're much of a cop,
但我觉得你是真想扳倒普罗科特
but I think you're serious about getting Proctor.
这个镇子一直在
And this town's been waiting
等待你这样的人  等了很久
for somebody to do that for a long, long time.
警长  你知道他们为什么怕我吗
Sheriff, do you know why they're afraid of me?
为什么
Why is that?
因为他们应该怕我
Because they should be.
或许你也应该怕我
And maybe you should be, too.
你没有证据  没有尸体
You have no evidence, no body,
连一个名字你都给不出
not even a name you say.
你会把他送进监狱吗
Would you put him away?
你到底能不能把他关起来
Could you even put him away?
有罪裁决可能要蹲五年监狱
A guilty verdict could mean five years in prison.
不行
Not acceptable.
我会想尽办法延缓判决进程
I-- I will file every motion I can to slow the process down,
除非有奇迹
but barring a miracle,
不然你的案子一定会由陪审团裁决
your case is gonna be decided by a jury.
那就等你给我创造奇迹了
Then a miracle is exactly what you're gonna get me.
明白吗
You get it?
-喂  -凯  我是艾米丽
- Yeah? - Kai, it's Emily.
你母亲病情恶化了
Your mother's taken a turn.
快回家来吧
You should come home now.
她时间不多了
She doesn't have much time.
谢谢你  艾米丽
Thank you, Emily.
我马上来
I'm on my way.
你最好给我搞定
You fucking fix this.
打烊了
We're closed.
走开
Leave.
-滚出去  -你到底想干什么
- Get out. - What the hell are you doing?
你最好赶紧走
You need to leave now.
你管你有什么事  警长  现在不行
Whatever it is, Sheriff, it has to wait.
不要啊
No!
天呐
Jesus.
叫警察啊
Call the police.
他就是警察
Uh, he is the police.
他妈的
God damn it.
胡德
Hood!
来  起来吧
Come on. Get up.
起来
Get up.
你没事吧
You okay?
凯·普罗科特  你因攻击警察被逮捕了
Kai Proctor, you're under arrest for assaulting an officer.
等等  这是自卫行为
Whoa, whoa. It was self-defense.
-胡德先动的手  -后退
- Hood attacked him first. - Back up or
不然连你一起抓
I'll cuff your ass, too.
去你奶奶那  她需要你
Go to your grandmother. She needs you.
走吧
Yeah, let's go.
抱歉久等了
Sorry for the wait.
你们现在都可以回去了
You can all head back now.
警长现在不在
The sheriff will need just a few minutes.
走吧
Go.
有何贵干
May I help you?
我想见警长  谢谢
I would like to speak to the sheriff, please.
你们有约吗
Is he expecting you?
-没有  女士  -请坐
- No, ma'am. - Take a seat.
不如这样  你去那边等吧
On second thought, go wait back there.
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
这可比骚扰严重多了
This is beyond harassment.
我有很多目击者
I've got a dozen witnesses
可以作证是你先出手打架的
who will testify that you started the fight.
-你他妈闭嘴好吗  -搞什么飞机
- Why don't you shut the fuck up? - What the hell happened?
-他差点谋杀了我的客户  -我没在问你
- He tried to murder my client. - I wasn't asking you.
你知道这对我们有多不利吗
Do you have any idea how bad this looks?
爷一点儿都不在乎
Ask me if I care.
-胡德  -别过来
- Hood. - Stay!
你好啊  农场小子
What's up, farm boy?
你们三个好好玩
You three play nice.
胡德
Hey, Hood.
好吧  别担心  我来搞定
Yeah, don't worry. I got this.
我不会告发你的
I'm not gonna turn you in.
不是因为我不想
Not because I don't want to,
而是因为真相会让这个警局崩溃
but because the truth would annihilate this department.
它会让所有真警察
It would wipe away
在这里做的努力都付之东流
all the good work real cops have done around here.
你知道我想好好做警察的
You know I tried to do good with that badge.
那个警徽从来就不是你的
That badge was never yours to wear.
兔子曾是你的老板吗
Rabbit was your boss?
你曾为他偷窃过吗
You stole for him?
是的
Yes.
还有卡莉·霍普韦尔  你们曾是...
And Carrie Hopewell, the two of you were...
-是的  -天哪
- Yes. - Jesus.
为什么是我
Why me?
西沃恩  不管你怎么想
Siobhan, no matter what you think,
但我们的感情是真的
you and me was not a lie.
西沃恩  我向上帝发誓
Siobhan, I swear to God.
我唯一觉得安全的时候
The only time I ever felt safe
就是和你在一起
was with you.
我信任你  我接纳了你
I trusted you. I let you in.
-我懂  -你使我的生命职业都处于险境  我还不知情
- I know. - You endangered my life, my career, and I let you.
-西沃恩  -不要
- Siobhan. - No.
你他妈别碰我
Don't fuckin' touch me.
我告诉你
This is what you're gonna do.
你现在出去
You're gonna go out there right now,
录完普罗科特的口供
you're gonna finish booking Proctor,
然后悄悄地辞职
and then you're gonna quietly resign.
然后呢
Then what?
然后你离开这里
And then you're gonna walk away.
趴下
Get down!